(Penny:)Bernadette, for every episode
of Doctor Who
(Penny:)Leonard has made me sit through,
(Penny:)I will play on your behalf
(Penny:)and send that TARDIS
back to Gallifrey,
(Penny:)where I hate
that I know it belongs.
(Bernadette:)Yes, Penny
plays for me.
(Howard:)That's not fair--
she has upper body muscles.
(Raj:)Dude, three-time
Sanskriti School
(Raj:)for Well-Born Boys
badminton champion.
(Howard:)That's right-- okay,
Raj can play for me.
(Amy:)Ooh, you just chose champions.
(Amy:)It's like we're reenacting
the ancient German practice
(Amy:)of trial by combat.
PENNY: Yeah,
it's also like
(Penny:)when the Mountain fought the
Red Viper in Game of Thrones.
(Bernadette:)Leonard makes you
watch that, too?
(Penny:)No, no, I like that show.
(Penny:)It's got dragons
and people doing it.
WOLOWITZ:
So it's settled.
(Howard:)The fate of Doctor Who's TARDIS
will be decided
by a Game of Thrones inspired
death-match on the battlefield
(Howard:)of ThunderCats
versus Transformers.
(Amy:)If you still have that bra,
I'll give you a nickel for it.
(Sheldon:)There it is.
(Sheldon:)It's just a gate.